Welcome to the libpromeki SubRip test file!
This cue has two lines (this one):
and one more (this other one)
Top-centered using \an8 anchor.
Middle-center using \an5 anchor.
Bottom-left using \an1 anchor.
Bounded by the X1/X2/Y1/Y2 coordinate hint.
This text should display italic.
Bold and underlined mixed inline.
Red text via inline font tag.
It flies like a truck.
What's a truck?
Café — naïve façade — résumé. UTF-8 round-trip.
Google tells me this is how you say Hello World in Japanese:
こんにちは世界
Big-boo-tay! Tay! Tay!
Numbers: 0123456789. Punctuation: .,;:!?"'()[]{}+-*/=<>@#$%^&
A longer single line that exercises the encoder's char-pair scheduler more thoroughly than a short cue.
This cue uses a period for the millisecond separator (WebVTT style).
Three-line cue body:
middle line, neither short nor long
bottom line wraps the block
Leading and trailing spaces in this cue.
Remember: No matter where you go, there you are.
Bottom-center anchor (the SubRip default for captioning).
Top-right anchor with X1:200 Y1:30 marker context.
Plain cue, no anchor, no markup, no special characters.
End of test file, this is the last subtitle.
History is-a made at night. Character is what you are in the dark.